hitsblender.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy | HitsBlender - Free Unlimited Music Online

Welcome to HitsBlender! This Privacy Policy is effective for HitsBlender («HitsBlender», «we», «us» and/or «our») and it applies to the HitsBlender website and associated pages (the «Site»), the content directory, tools, and applications (together with the Site, the «Service»).

We will continue to evaluate this Privacy Policy and update it accordingly when there is a change to our business practices, our users’ needs, and to comply with regulatory and legal requirements. Please check this page periodically for updates. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy here and notify you by email or by means of a notice on our website.

## Collection of Personal Information

We do not collect email addresses or any personally identifiable information on visitors to our site. We do not use our site for any commercial transactions.

## Terms of Service

Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our service.

## Automatic Data Collection

**Listening Activity:** We keep track of your listening activity. We collect information about stations, favorites, artists and tracks you have listened to or in which you have expressed an interest.

**Information about your computer or  device:** We may also collect information about the computer, mobile or other devices you use to access the Service. For example, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, operating system, browser type, and other software or hardware information.

**Location-based information:** On our Site, we do not collect your zip code, postal code, city or country. Your general geo-location is collected at regular intervals if you use the Service on your mobile device. We collect this information to provide content and services that are customized for your geographic area.

**Tracking technology:** We use what are commonly called «cookies» on our Site. A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Site gives to your browser when you access the Site. These cookies help us improve the Service, provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. We may also be able to capture other data such as searches conducted and results, date, time, and connection speed. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect personal.

## Non-Identifiable or Aggregated Data

We also receive and store certain non-personally identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. We may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by our affiliates, agents or service providers. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Service. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Service, we often conduct research on our customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the personal information and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. We may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

The use and disclosure of this non-personally identifiable information is not subject to restrictions under this Privacy Policy.

## How we protect your information

We have taken reasonable steps to protect the personal information provided via the Service from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet, email or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, so you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us in this way.

## English language version shall control

The English language version of this Privacy Policy is the version that governs your use of the Service and in the event of any conflict between the English language version and a translated version, the English language version will control.

## Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the privacy practices of HitsBlender, email to [info@hitsblender.com](mailto:info@hitsblender.com).
